vividforfree.com 2004-11-14

# Privacy Statement for LFP, Inc.

**Privacy Statement for LFP, Inc.**

LFP, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.      

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site's subscription form requires users to give us contact information (to include names and E-mail addresses), financial information (to include account or credit card numbers). We use customer contact information from the subscription form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. LFP, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other such websites. Selection of an ad banner or link redirects User to a third party. Transactions that occur between the User and the third party are strictly between the User and the third party and are not the responsibility of LFP, Inc. Because LFP, Inc. is not responsible for the availability of these outside resources or their privacy policy or content, User should direct any concerns regarding any external link to its site administrator or Webmaster. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (to include E-mail addresses), and financial information (to include account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and to bill the user for products and services ordered. 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**To Opt Out of receiving future mailings and/or promotions:**

  1. You can send email to support@hustler.com 
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address: 

Consumer Protection Dept.  
5701 Lindero Canyon Road #2-200  
Westlake Village, CA 91362 

**To Deactivate your membership:**

  1. Call the following telephone number: 1-888-205-0489 
  2. Visit http://www.internetventures.com 
  3. Send an e-mail to: help@cs.billingservices.com
